{
    "id": "25b7d5605b6b4a2ab054da40dc28fee3",
    "title": "Relative pronouns: exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "89676242c24046ca8f4d636ae20a9aca",
            "title": "Relative Pronouns Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "We all trust people ………………….. speak the truth.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "who",
                        "whom",
                        "which"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He ……………………. does his best shall be rewarded.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "who",
                        "that",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I don’t understand …………………… you mean.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "that",
                        "what",
                        "which"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She has gone to Bangalore, ………………… is her birth place.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "which",
                        "that",
                        "what"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You should learn to give away ……………………… you do not need.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "which",
                        "that",
                        "what"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "There is no one ……………………… has not lost a dear one.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "who",
                        "whom",
                        "that"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "You get …………………….. you deserve.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "that",
                        "what",
                        "which"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is a person ……………………. you can trust.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "who",
                        "whom",
                        "that"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The letter ……………………. he sent never reached me.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "which",
                        "that",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He ……………………… treats others with kindness will be treated with kindness.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "who",
                        "that",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}